clothingshoponline.com 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy | Clothing Shop Online

1.  Acceptance of Terms

Welcome to **www.clothingshoponline.com** (the “ **Site** ”), a web site operated on behalf of Clothing Shop Online LLC (“ **CSO** ”, “ **us** ,” “ **we** ” and “ **our** ”). Your privacy is important to us. It is our policy to protect your Personal Information (as defined below) and to use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Using our Site is voluntary, and by using the Site, you consent to our collection and use of your identifying and non-identifying information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only governs our use and disclosure of information collected through this Site.

2.  Information We Collect From You

**Non-Personal Information**

We automatically collect information about your Internet connection, including but not limited to: the name of the Internet domain you used to access the Internet; the IP address of the web site from which you linked directly to our Site; the connection speed/screen resolution/browser used; the date and time you accessed our Site; and the pages you visited. This information (“ **Non-Personal Information** ”) does not identify you personally. We use this Non-Personal Information to monitor the effectiveness of the Site and to consider potential improvements to the Site.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

You are able to view and download certain content displayed on the Site without disclosing any information that, either alone or in combination with other information, can be used to uniquely identify, contact or locate you (collectively, “ **Personally Identifiable Information,” or “PII** ”). However, certain features accessible through the Site may require disclosure of certain PII, depending upon the features you are using.

**Registered Users**

Access to certain portions of the Site may require login and password information provided only to users who have registered (each a “ **Registered User** ”). **** As part of the registration process, ClothingShopOnline may collect certain PII including your name, address, email address and other PII you disclose to us. By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Order Entry and Payment**

In connection with your requests for goods, services and/or information, ClothingShopOnline may collect certain PII including: contact information, such as your name, address, email address and phone number, financial information, such as your credit card number, expiration date and billing address, and other PII you disclose to us. Your credit card information is encrypted and provided to the credit card issuer for verification and approval. We do not retain any credit card information.  By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Policy.

3.  Use of Your Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to administer your participation in the Site and to communicate information we think may be of interest to you, which may include newsletters, alerts, special promotional offers, consumer surveys and other promotional or informational messages. If you no longer wish to receive such messages, simply click the 'unsubscribe' link that we include at the bottom of every email that we send you. If a different opt-out mechanism is provided in any individual message, please follow the directions included within that specific email.

4.  Sharing Your Information

We may use third party service providers and suppliers to assist us in administering the Site and providing the services we offer, and to that end, they may have access to your Personal Information. In addition, we may buy or sell business assets or be acquired by or acquire other corporations. In such transactions, Personal Information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In addition, in the event we merge or consolidate with another institution, your Personal Information may be transferred to the successor entity. We may also disclose your Personal Information to other affiliated institutions and/or if we are required to do so by law.

5.  Use of Cookies

Cookies are small bits of data cached or stored on your computer through your web browser based on Internet activity. We may use cookies to monitor individual user activity or activity of users in aggregate to improve the Service and provide features that are tailored to your needs, including delivery of customized content and advertising. The information we gather may include IP address, user language, the operating system, browser type, the presence/absence of “flash” plug-ins, screen resolution, connection type, and information that identifies the cookie. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent this. If you disable cookies, your ability to use some features of the Service may be limited. We also use session cookies when you visit the Site. The session cookie allows our server to reconnect your incoming request with previously stored session-collected data.  The cookie persists until you close your browser, or up to six (6) months, depending on the type of session cookie.

6.  Linked Sites

We may provide links on the Site to other sites of interest. We do not review or endorse the content of these sites or guarantee that they will abide by this Privacy Policy. Your use of such linked sites is subject to the privacy policies of the providers of those sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each Site that collects Personal Information.

7.  Security Measures

We strive to maintain the security of your information by using reasonable and appropriate technical, physical and administrative safeguards, including encryption technology, particularly, in connection with the order entry and payment functionality.  However, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online. Consequently, we do not insure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.

8.  Children and Parents

Use of the Site is not offered to children. If you are under 13, you may not use the Site. We do not intend to collect personal information from children. Parents and guardians are advised that any personal information voluntarily entered by children may be available for public access. If your child has submitted personal information, please contact us to request that such information be removed. Once we are aware of information entered by a child, we will exercise commercially reasonable efforts to remove such information from our database; however, we are not liable for any consequences relating to such information.

9.  Reviewing Information

You may review your Personal Information stored in your profile by logging into the Site. You may change your contact information, including your name and mailing address. In the event you are unable to change your Personal Information, please email help@clothingshoponline.com. You may also email help@clothingshoponline.com regarding any issues about your Personal Information.

10.  Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. If we do make a change, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. Questions, comments or complaints about our privacy policies should be submitted to us at help@clothingshoponline.com.

Effective Date: July 25, 2012
